好吧，让我们开始
all right let's get started
这是682的分布式系统等等
this is 682 for distributed systems so
我想开始只是简单的
I'd like to start with just a brief
什么，我想解释
explanation of what I think a
分布式系统是你知道的核心
distributed system is you know the core
它是一组协作计算机
of it is a set of cooperating computers
被彼此进行通信
that are communicating with each other
网络上得到一些连贯的任务
over networked to get some coherent task
这样网络的各种例子说
done and so the kinds of examples that
我们将重点放在本类中
we'll be focusing on in this class are
之类的东西储存大网站或
things like storage for big websites or
大数据计算诸如MapReduce的
big data computations such as MapReduce
也有些更奇特的东西
and also somewhat more exotic things
像对等网络文件共享等等
like peer-to-peer file sharing so
他们都只是例子种
they're all just examples the kinds of
我们来看看案例研究，在与
case studies we'll look at and the
之所以这样，所有重要的是，
reason why all this is important is that
很多重要的基础设施出
a lot of critical infrastructure out
有内置了分布式
there is built out of distributed
需要系统的基础设施
systems infrastructure that requires
多台电脑，以获取其工作
more than one computer to get its job
完成或这有点内在需要
done or it's sort of inherently needs to
在物理上分散做的理由
be spread out physically so the reasons
人们为什么建立这个东西，所以第一
why people build this stuff so first of
所有我甚至谈论分发前
all before I even talk about distributed
系统之类的提醒你，你知道
systems sort of remind you that you know
如果你正在设计一个系统，重新设计
if you're designing a system redesigning
你需要解决，如果你的一些问题
you need to solve some problem if you
都不可能解决它在一个单一
can possibly solve it on a single
计算机，你知道不建
computer you know without building a
分布式系统，你应该做的是
distributed system you should do it that
方式有很多很多的工作，你可以
way and there's many many jobs you can
获得一台计算机上完成的，它是
get done on a single computer and it's
总是比较容易使分布式系统你
always easier so distributed systems you
知道你应该尝试一切
know you should try everything else
然后再尝试构建分布式
before you try building distributed
系统，因为他们不是他们不
systems because they're not they're not
简单所以人们为什么的原因
simpler so the reason why people are
驱动使用大量的合作
driven to use lots of cooperating
电脑是他们需要得到
computers are they need to get
高性能和思维方式
high-performance and the way to think
关于这就是他们想要得到实现
about that is they want to get achieve
某种并行地段的CPU的
some sort of parallelism lots of CPUs
很多回忆大量的磁盘臂的
lots of memories lots of disk arms
平行移动的另一个原因
moving in parallel another reason why
人们建立这种东西是要能够
people build this stuff is to be able to
容忍故障
tolerate faults
有两台电脑做同样的
have two computers do the exact same
如果事情他们中的一个失败，您可以切
thing if one of them fails you can cut
到另一个另一个原因是，
over to the other one another is that
有些问题只是自然传播
some problems are just naturally spread
在太空中像你知道你想
out in space like you know you want to
做钱跨行转账或
do interbank transfers of money or
东西好，你知道银行有这个
something well you know bank a has this
电脑在纽约市和B银行作为
computer in New York City and Bank B as
这台计算机在伦敦，你知道你
this computer in London you know you
只是有一些办法来为他们
just have to have some way for them to
互相交谈和合作，
talk to each other and cooperate in
为了携带出这么有一些
order to carry that out so there's some
自然排序物理原因系统
natural sort of physical reasons systems
这本质上是物理
that are inherently physically
分布式的最终原因，
distributed for the final reason that
人们建立这个东西是为了
people build this stuff is in order to
实现某种形式的安全目标，使
achieve some sort of security goal so
常常，如果有一些代码，你不
often by if there's some code you don't
信托或你知道你需要互动
trust or you know you need to interact
与某人，但你知道他们可能不
with somebody but you know they may not
是即时的恶意或者也许他们
be immediate malicious or maybe their
代码中有错误，所以你不想
code has bugs in it so you don't want to
要相信它，你可能需要分割
have to trust it you may want to split
起来计算，所以你知道你的
up the computation so you know your
东西跑那边那台电脑
stuff runs over there and that computer
我的东西在这里运行在这台计算机上，并
my stuff runs here on this computer and
他们只说给对方一些
they only talk to each other to some
排序窄狭义的网络的
sort of narrow narrowly defined network
协议假设我们可能会担心
protocol assuming we may be worried
你知道的安全，这就是
about you know security and that's
通过拆分东西到实现
achieved by splitting things up into
多台电脑，让他们可以
multiple computers so that they can be
分离出的最这当然是
isolated the most of this course is
将是关于性能和故障
going to be about performance and fault
宽容虽然经常另外两个
tolerance although the other two often
通过那种方式本身工作
work themselves in by way of the sort of
在案例研究的限制
constraints on the case studies that
我们要看看你知道所有
we're going to look at you know all
这些分布式系统，使这些
these distributed systems so these
问题是，因为他们有很多
problems are because they have many
零件和部件并发执行
parts and the parts execute concurrently
因为有多个计算机，您
because there are multiple computers you
得到所有搞出问题
get all the problems that come up with
并发编程的所有排序
concurrent programming all the sort of
复杂的相互作用和我们
complex interactions and we're
时间相关的东西，这就是部分
timing-dependent stuff and that's part
是什么使分布式系统硬
of what makes distributed systems hard
这使得分布式另一件事
another thing that makes distributed
系统硬盘是因为你再次
systems hard is that because again you
拥有多条加一个网络，你
have multiple pieces plus a network you
可以有很意外故障
can have very unexpected failure
模式，就是如果你有一个
patterns that is if you have a single
计算机它通常是两种情况
computer it's usually the case either
计算机工程或可能崩溃或
computer works or maybe it crashes or
遭受停电或东西，但
suffers a power failure or something but
它几乎无论是工作还是不
it pretty much either works or doesn't
大量的由工作分布式系统
work distributed systems made up of lots
电脑，你可以有偏
of computers you can have partial
失败是一些停止件
failures that is some pieces stopped
工作的其他人的其他作品
working other people other pieces
继续工作或者也许是电脑
continue working or maybe the computers
正在但是网络的某些部分
are working but some part of the network
损坏或不可靠的这样的部分
is broken or unreliable so partial
失败的另一个原因是
failures is another reason why
分布式系统是很难和最终
distributed systems are hard and a final
之所以很难的，你知道
reason why it's hard is that you know
他们当初之所以建
them the original reason to build the
分布式系统往往能得到
distributed system is often to get
更高的性能，让你知道
higher performance to get you know a
千台电脑价值表现
thousand computers worth of performance
甚至上千元盘武器是的
or a thousand disk arms were the
性能，但它实际上是非常
performance but it's actually very
棘手的获得千倍速
tricky to obtain that thousand X speed
了一千台计算机有
up with a thousand computers there's
往往很多路障扔在你
often a lot of roadblocks thrown in your
方式，使精灵需要一点谨慎
way so the Elven takes a bit of careful
设计使系统实际上给
design to make the system actually give
你表现你觉得你值得拥有
you the performance you feel you deserve
所以解决，当然这些问题
so solving these problems of course
将是所有关于你知道
going to be all about you know
解决这些问题的原因
addressing these issues the reason to
参加课程，是因为经常
take the course is because often the
问题和解决办法都相当
problems and the solutions are quite
只是技术上有趣他们
just technically interesting they're
对于其中一些问题难题
hard problems for some of these problems
有已知相当不错的解决方案
there's pretty good solutions known for
他们没有这么大的其他问题
other problems they're not such great
现在的解决方案分发系统
solutions now distributed systems are
使用了大量真实世界系统的出
used by a lot of real-world systems out
有喜欢大的网站经常参与
there like big websites often involved
你知道广大计算机是
you know vast numbers computers that are
你知道放在一起作为分布式
you know put together as distributed
当我刚开始教学系统
systems when I first started teaching
这当然是分布式系统
this course it was distributed systems
的学术好奇心是什么
were something of an academic curiosity
你认识的人还以为哦，你知道在
you know people thought oh you know at a
他们有时被用于小规模
small scale they were used sometimes and
人们觉得，哦，有一天他们会
people felt that oh someday they'd be
可能是重要的，但现在特别
might be important but now particularly
由巨人网站的兴起带动
driven by the rise of giant websites
有你知道的海量数据
that have you know vast amounts of data
和整个仓库完全电脑
and entire warehouses full of computers
在过去的分布式系统
distributed systems in the last
二十年变得非常
twenty years have gotten to be very
计算的严重重要组成部分
seriously important part of computing
基础设施，这意味着有
infrastructure this means that there's
得到了很多的关注支付给他们
been a lot of attention paid to them a
很多问题都已经解决了，但
lot of problems have been solved but
仍有不少未解
there's still quite a few unsolved
所以，如果你是一个研究生的问题
problems so if you're a graduate student
或者你感兴趣的研究有
or you're interested in research there's
很多你让很多问题还没有
a lot to you let a lot of problems yet
在分布式系统要解决的是
to be solved in distributed systems that
你可以看看他的研究和
you could look into his research and
最后，如果你喜欢的东西建立这个
finally if you like building stuff this
是善类，因为它有一个实验室
is a good class because it has a lab
在你构建一些序列
sequence in which you'll construct some
相当现实的分布式系统
fairly realistic distributed systems
专注于性能和故障
focused on performance and fault
公差
tolerance
所以你有大量的实践建设
so you've got a lot of practice building
区仅有构建分布式
districts just building distributed
系统，使他们的工作好吗
systems and making them work all right
让我谈谈课程结构有点
let me talk about course structure a bit
之前，我开始真实技术
before I get started on real technical
内容，你应该能够找到
content you should be able to find the
使用谷歌和在球场上的网站
course website using Google and on the
当然网站是实验室作业
course website is the lab assignments
和课程安排，并链接到一个
and course schedule and also link to a
广场页面，您可以张贴问题
Piazza page where you can post questions
得到答案的过程中的工作人员，我罗伯特
get answers the course staff I'm Robert
莫里斯我会给予我的讲座
Morris I'll be giving the lectures I
也有TAS你们要站
also have for TAS you guys want to stand
并显示你的面孔是TAS
up and show your faces the TAS are
在特定的专家做
experts at in particular at doing the
解决他们会拿着实验室
solving the labs they'll be holding
上班时间，所以如果您有任何疑问
office hours so if you have questions
有关实验室你能来你应该
about the labs you can come you should
去办公时间，或者你可以发布
go to office hours or you could post
问题来广场的过程中有一个
questions to Piazza the course has a
几个重要的组成部分之一是
couple of important components one is
这个演讲有一个纸差不多
this lectures there's a paper for almost
每次讲座有两个考试
every lecture there's two exams
有编程实验室的实验室和
there's the labs programming labs and
还有一个可选的最终项目
there's an optional final project that
你可以做的实验室之一，而不是
you can do instead of one of the labs
讲座将左右两个大思路
the lectures will be about two big ideas
在分布式系统中他们也将是一个
in distributed systems they'll also be a
夫妇讲座是更多
couple of lectures that are more about
排序的实验室编程的东西很多
sort of lab programming stuff a lot of
我们的演讲会的情况下采取了
our lectures will be taken up by case
研究了很多方式，我有点
studies a lot of the way that I sort of
尽量带出的内容
try to bring out the content of
分布式系统通过观察
distributed systems is by looking at
论文有学者通过一些书面
papers some academics some written by
人们在业内真正描述
people in industry describing real
解决实际问题
solutions to real problems
这些讲座其实是可以录像
these lectures actually be videotaped
而我希望能在网上发布他们如此
and I'm hoping to post them online so
你可以这样，如果你不在这里，或者
that you can so if you're not here or
要查看你会讲座
you want to review the lectures you'll
能看录像带
be able to look at the videotape
讲座试卷再有一到
lectures the papers again there's one to
每周读一大部分研究论文
read per week most of a research paper
他们中的一些经典论文像
some of them are classic papers like
今天的报纸上，我希望你们中的一些
today's paper which I hope some of you
已阅读的MapReduce这是一个旧纸
have read on MapReduce it's an old paper
但它是在其刺激的开始
but it was the beginning of its spurred
有趣的工作，大量的
an enormous amount of interesting work
学术和现实世界中的那么
both academic and in the real world so
有些是经典的，有些是更
some are classic and some are more
最近的论文之类的谈论更多
recent papers sort of talking about more
达最新研究什么人都
up-to-date research what people are
目前担心，并从
currently worried about and from the
我们将希望论文梳理出什么
papers we'll be hoping to tease out what
基本的问题是观念的人是什么
the basic problems are what ideas people
有可能会或可能不会
have had that might or might not be
在解决分布式系统中有用
useful in solving distributed system
我们将着眼于有时问题
problems we'll be looking at sometimes
在一些实施细节
in implementation details in some of
这些文章，因为很多这有
these papers because a lot of this has
做的实际施工
to do with actual construction of of
基于软件的系统和我们也
software based systems and we're also
要花费一定的时间在看
going to spend a certain time looking at
评估人员评估如何故障
evaluations people evaluating how fault
通过测量，宽容他们的系统
tolerant their systems by measuring them
或者人们衡量多少性能
or people measuring how much performance
或者他们是否得到了性能
or whether they got performance
改善在所有所以我希望，
improvement at all so I'm hoping that
你来之前，阅读文件
you'll read the papers before coming to
类讲座也许不会
class the lectures are maybe not going
让尽可能多的意义，如果你还没有
to make as much sense if you haven't
已经阅读讲座，因为有
already read the lecture because there's
没有足够的时间来解释两者都
not enough time to both explaining all
本文的内容和有几分
the content of the paper and have a sort
什么有趣的反思
of interesting reflection on what the
纸是指在线课程让你真正
paper means online class so you really
赶紧去读读报纸我来之前
got to read the papers before I come
进入阶级和的一个有希望
into class and hopefully one of the
的东西，你将学习在这个类是如何
things you'll learn in this class is how
在鱼迅速读报纸
to read a paper rapidly in the fish
而在部分跳过，也许
and skip over the parts that maybe
并不是那么重要和排序的重点
aren't that important and sort of focus
对梳理出的重要思想
on teasing out the important ideas on
该网站有一个为每个环节
the website there's for every link to
购买计划有这么一个问题
buy the schedule there's a question that
你应该提交的答案
you should submit an answer for for
每一个文件，我认为答案是由于
every paper I think the answers are due
在午夜，我们也请您
at midnight and we also ask that you
提交你对一个问题
submit a question you have about the
通过网站纸张，以便既
paper through the website in order both
给我一些思考的
to give me something to think about as
我准备演讲，如果我有
I'm preparing the lecture and if I have
一次，我会尽量回答至少有几个
time I'll try to answer at least a few
通过电子邮件和问题
of the questions by email and the
问题并为每个文件的答案
question and the answer for each paper
由于半夜还有前一天晚上
due midnight the night before there's
两个考试有一个期中考试中
two exams there's a midterm exam in
类我觉得在最后一堂课会议
class I think on the last class meeting
前春假，有一个最终的
before spring break and there's a final
在结束时最后考试周考试
exam during final exam week at the end
本学期的考试要
of the semester the exams are going to
主要集中在论文和实验室和
focus mostly on papers and the labs and
大概做准备的最好方法
probably the best way to prepare for
他们以及听课和
them as well as attending lecture and
看报的好办法准备
reading the papers a good way to prepare
对于考试是看所有考试我们
for the exams is to look at all exams we
有联系的20岁的考试和
have links to 20 years of old exams and
解决方案，所以你看那些和
solutions and so you look at those and
排序得到什么样的感觉
sort of get a feel for what kind of
问题，我想问一下，确实
questions that I like to ask and indeed
因为我们看到许多相同的论文
because we read many of the same papers
不可避免地我每年提问
inevitably I ask questions each year
这不禁类似问题
that can't help but resemble questions
问往年实验室有
asked in previous years the labs there's
编程实验室的第一个
for programming labs the first one of
他们是将于周五公布下周的实验室之一
them is due Friday next week lab one is
一个简单的MapReduce的实验室，以实现你
a simple MapReduce lab to implement your
自己的版本，他们写论文的
own version of the paper they write
今天我将在一个被讨论
today in which I'll be discussing in a
几分钟
few minutes
实验室2涉及使用一种被称为
lab 2 involves using a technique called
筏，以获得故障教
raft in order to get fault taught in
为了某种允许在理论上允许
order to sort of allow in theory allow
任何系统通过进行容错
any system to be made fault tolerant by
复制它，有这个木筏
replicating it and having this raft
技术管理复制和
technique manage the replication and
排序管理自动切
manage sort of automatic cut
或者，如果有一个领域，如果的一个
or if there's a field if one of the
复制服务器失败，所以这是RAV4
replicated servers fails so this is rav4
容错在孩子3，你会用你的
fault tolerance in lad 3 you'll use your
为了实现筏建一个
raft implementation in order to build a
容错键值服务器时，它会
fault tolerant key-value server it'll be
复制并在实验室4容错
replicated and fault tolerant in a lab 4
你把你复制的键值
you'll take your replicated key-value
服务器和克隆成若干
server and clone it into a number of
独立团体，你会分裂
independent groups and you'll split the
在您的键值存储系统数据
data in your key value storage system
在所有这些个别的
across all of these individual
复制组以获得并行
replicated groups to get parallel
加速运行多个复制
speed-up by running multiple replicated
平行组，那么您也
groups in parallel and you'll also be
负责移动各
responsible for moving the various
不同服务器之间的数据块
chunks of data between different servers
他们来去无任何下降
as they come and go without dropping any
球，所以这是一个什么通常被称为
balls so this is a what's often called a
分片键值服务分片
sharded key value service sharding
是指拆分数据
refers to splitting up the data
分隔多个间的数据
partitioning the data among multiple
为了服务器以获得并行速度
servers in order to get parallel speed
如果你还想而不是做实验室4
up if you want instead of doing lab 4
你可以做你自己选择的项目
you can do a project of your own choice
和这里的想法是，如果你有一些
and the idea here is if you have some
主意，你知道分布式系统
idea for a distributed system you know
在一些分布式的风格
in the style of some of the distributed
我们在课堂上，如果谈到系统
systems we talked about in the class if
你有自己的想法，你想
you have your own idea that you want to
追求你喜欢建立的东西
pursue and you like to build something
并测量其是否为了工作
and measure whether it worked in order
探索你的想法，你可以做一个
to explore your idea you can do a
工程等的项目，你会挑
project and so for a project you'll pick
一些队友，因为我们要求
some teammates because we require that
项目中的两个或团队完成
projects are done in teams of two or
三个人那么像一些队友和
three people so like some teammates and
把你的项目的想法我们，我们将
send your project idea to us and we'll
想想看，说是或否，
think about it and say yes or no and
也许给你一些建议，然后，如果
maybe give you some advice and then if
你继续前进，如果我们说是做的，
you go ahead and do if we say yes and
你想做的事你做一个项目，和
you want to do a project you do that and
的实验室4，而不是和它的原因在最后
instead of lab 4 and it's due at the end
这个学期，你知道你会你
of the semester and you know you'll you
应该做一些设计工作，并建立一个
should do some design work and build a
真正的系统，然后在最后一天
real system and then in the last day of
类，你会证明你的系统
class you'll demonstrate your system
以及在很短的那种移交
as well as handing in a short sort of
什么，你给我们书面报告
written report to us about what you
建造和我在网站上发布了一些
built and I posted on the website some
一些想法，这可能会或可能不会
some ideas which might or may not be
对你有用排序冲动的想法
useful for you to sort of spur thoughts
什么项目，你可能建造，但
about what projects you might build but
真的是最好的项目之一，
really the best projects are one where
那种你的一个好主意
sort of you have a good idea for the
项目和想法是，如果你想
project and the idea is if you want to
做一个项目，你应该选择一个想法
do a project you should choose an idea
这是那种在同样的
that's sort of in the same vein as the
在这个被谈论了系统
systems that were talked about in this
类
class
还好回到实验室实验室贪婪是他们
okay back to labs the lab Greed's they
我们给你的手在你的实验室代码
we give you you hand in your lab code
我们运行一些测试反对，
and we run some tests against it and
你是一位伟大的基础上有多少
you're great early based on how many
你通过考试，我们给你所有的测试
tests you pass we give you all the tests
我们使用那些没有任何隐藏的测试，所以如果
that we use those no hidden tests so if
您可靠地实现了实验室，并
you implement the lab and it reliably
通过了所有测试和机会
passes all the tests and chances are
好了，除非有一些有趣的事情
good unless there's something funny
去上有时存在
going on which there sometimes is
有很好的机会，如果你的COOP
chances are good that if you your coop
当你运行它还是通过了所有测试
passes all the tests when you run it or
通过所有的测试，当我们运行它，
pass all the tests when we run it and
你会得到一个4个评分满分如此
you'll get a four score full score so
希望以后还有没有关于谜
hopefully there'll be no mystery about
多少分你可能得上
what score you're likely to get on the
实验室让我提醒你，调试
labs let me warn you that debugging
这些实验室可以耗费时间，因为
these labs can be time-consuming because
他们分布式系统和大量的
they're distributed systems and a lot of
并发和通信类的
concurrency and communication sort of
奇怪的难以调试错误可能
strange difficult to debug errors can
突然出现，所以你真的应该开始
crop up so you really ought to start the
实验室早不这样做，甚至不会有很多
labs early don't don't even have a lot
的麻烦，如果你要经过到最后
of trouble if you be elapsed to the last
此刻你有，如果提前启动
moment you got to start early if your
问题请到办公室TAS
problems please come to the TAS office
小时，请随时提问
hours and please feel free to ask
关于广场和实验室问题
questions about the labs on Piazza and
事实上，我希望，如果你知道答案
indeed I hope if you know the answer
你会回答人的问题上
that you'll answer people's questions on
广场以及所有的权利有任何疑问
Piazza as well all right any questions
关于课程的机制是
about the mechanics of the course yes
所以问题是什么，是怎么做怎么样
so the question is what is how does how
做不同的因素，这些东西
do the different factor these things
融通级我忘了，但它
factoring the grade I forget but it's
所有在它的下网站
all on the it's on the website under
一句话，我认为虽然这是实验室
something I think though it's the labs
是一个最重要的组成部分
are the single most important component
好吧好吧，所以这是一个关于课程
okay alright so this is a course about
应用程序基础设施有关
about infrastructure for applications
所以在这整个过程中有
and so all through this course there's
将要在我的方式排序分裂
going to be a sort of split in the way I
谈谈应用程序之间的事情
talk about things between applications
这是某种其他人
which are sort of other people the
顾客别人写，但
customer somebody else writes but the
应用程序将使用
applications are going to use the
基础设施，我们正在考虑
infrastructure that we're thinking about
在这个过程中，因此该种
in this course and so the kinds of
基础设施，往往会拿出一个
infrastructure that tend to come up a
很多我们的存储和通信
lot our storage communication and
计算，我们将谈论系统
computation and we'll talk about systems
提供所有这三个种的
that provide all three of these kinds of
基础设施的存储事实
infrastructure the the storage it turns
指出，存储将是一个
out that storage is going to be the one
我们专注于最，因为这是一个非常
we focus most on because it's a very
明确定义和有用的抽象和
well-defined and useful abstraction and
通常相当简单
usually fairly straightforward
抽象让人们知道了很多关于
abstraction so people know a lot about
如何建立如何使用和构建
how to build how to use and build
存储系统以及如何构建排序
storage systems and how to build sort of
复制容错
replicated fault tolerant
高性能分布式
high-performance distributed
存储的实现，我们还将
implementations of storage we'll also
谈一些我们的一些计算
talk about some some of our computation
系统如MapReduce的今天是
systems like MapReduce for today is a
计算系统，我们将讨论
computation system and we will talk
有关通信的一些但大多是
about communications some but mostly
从点是一个工具，我们需要
from the point is a tool that we need to
用它来建立分布式系统，如
use to build distributed systems like
计算机具有相互交谈
computers have to talk to each other
在网络上，你也许知道你需要
over a network you know maybe you need
可靠性或东西，所以我们会
reliability or something and so we'll
讨论一下我们实际是
talk a bit about what we're actually
大多消费者的沟通，如果你
mostly consumers of communication if you
想了解通信
want to learn about communication
系统，排序它们是如何工作的是的
systems as sort of how they work that's
六八到九点多的话题
more the topic of six eight to nine
所以对于存储和计算大量的
so for storage and computation a lot of
我们的目标是能够发现
our goal is to be able to discover
抽象其中使用简化的
abstractions where use of simplifying
的界面这两个存储和
the interface to these two storage and
计算分布式存储和
computation distributed storage and
计算基础设施，以便它
computation infrastructure so that it's
容易建立在它之上的应用
easy to build applications on top of it
什么是真正的意思是，我们
and what that really means is that we
需要我们希望能够建立
need to we'd like to be able to build
抽象，隐藏分布
abstraction that hide the distributed
这些这些系统的性质，因此
nature of these of these systems so the
梦想是很少完全实现，但
dream which is rarely fully achieved but
的梦想是能够建立
the dream would be to be able to build
一个界面，看起来到
an interface that looks to an
应用程序是，如果它的分布是非
application is if it's a non distributed
存储系统就像一个文件系统
storage system just like a file system
什么的，每个人都已经
or something that everybody already
知道如何编程，并具有相当
knows how to program and has a pretty
简单的模型语义我们很高兴能够成为
simple model semantics we'd love to be
能够建立接口，它们的外观和
able to build interfaces that look and
行为就像非分布式存储
act just like non distributed storage
和计算系统，但实际上
and computation systems but are actually
你知道广大极高的性能
you know vast extremely high performance
容错分布式系统
fault tolerant distributed systems
下面，所以我们都有抽象
underneath so we both have abstractions
你知道你会为一个疗程看看
and you know as you'll see as a course
接着我们那种只知道一部分
goes on we sort of you know only part of
途中有你找到它的罕见
the way there it's rare that you find an
抽象的分布式版本
abstraction for a distributed version of
存储或计算有简单
storage or computation that has simple
的行为，但他就像非刚
behavior but he's just like the non just
存储即非分布式版本
non distributed version of storage that
大家都明白，但人们越来越
everybody understands but people getting
在此更好，我们要去尝试
better at this and we're gonna try to
学习的方式和人有什么
study the ways and what people have
了解建立这样的抽象概念
learned about building such abstractions
好了，所以什么样什么样的话题
ok so what kind of what kind of topics
露面是我们正在考虑这些
show up is we're considering these
抽象的第一个此第一
abstractions the first one this first
话题常见的主题，我们会看到很多
topic general topic that we'll see a lot
很多系统中，我们看着都
a lot of the systems we looked at have
与实施这样做，例如
to do with implementation so for example
那种工具，你看到很多关于
the kind of tools that you see a lot for
办法的人学习如何建立这些
for ways people learn how to build these
系统之类的东西远程过程
systems are things like remote procedure
呼叫
call
其目的是掩盖事实
whose goal is to mask the fact that
我们在不可靠的通信
we're communicating over an unreliable
网络另一种实施
Network another kind of implementation
话题，我们会看到很多的线程
topic that we'll see a lot is threads
其是一种编程技术，
which are a programming technique that
让我们来线束什么可以让我们
allows us to harness what allows us to
线束多核计算机，但也许
harness multi-core computers but maybe
该类线程更重要
more important for this class threads
是结构化并行的方式
are a way of structuring concurrent
在某种程度上这是希望的操作
operations in a way that's hopefully
简化那些的程序员视图
simplifies the programmer view of those
并行操作和，因为我们
concurrent operations and because we're
要使用线程大量事实证明
gonna use threads a lot it turns out
我们将需要你也知道
we're going to need to also you know
正如从实施层面
just as from an implementation level
花一定的时间思考
spend a certain amount of time thinking
关于并发控制之类的东西
about concurrency control things like
锁和主要场所，这些
locks and the main place that these
实施意见将拿出在
implementation ideas will come up in the
一流的，他们会在很多人被感动的
class they'll be touched on in many of
报纸，但你会来的脸
the papers but you're gonna come face
这一切的在一个大的方式在脸上
the face of all this in a big way in the
你需要建立实验室分布式您
labs you need to build distributed you
知道做编程分布式
know do the programming for distributed
系统，这些都是想了很多种类的
system and these are like a lot of sort
重要的工具，你知道不仅仅是
of important tools you know beyond just
那种普通的编程的这些
sort of ordinary programming these are
一些关键的工具，你会
some of the critical tools that you'll
需要用来构建分布式系统
need to use to build distributed systems
在所有出现的另一大话题
another big topic that comes up in all
报纸上我们要谈的是
the papers we're going to talk about is
性能通常是高层次的目标
performance usually the high-level goal
构建分布式系统是
of building a distributed system is to
让人们所说的可扩展提速
get what people call scalable speed-up
所以我们正在寻找的可扩展性和
so we're looking for scalability and
我所说的可扩展性和可扩展性
what I mean by scalability or scalable
加速是，如果我有一些问题
speed-up is that if I have some problem
说我有一台电脑和我解决
that I'm solving with one computer and I
买第二台电脑帮我执行
buy a second computer to help me execute
我的问题，如果我现在能解决
my problem if I can now solve the
在一半的时间问题，也许解决
problem in half the time or maybe solve
两倍多的问题情况下，你知道
twice as many problem instances you know
每两台计算机上作为分我对
per minute on two computers as I had on
一个那么这就是一个例子
one then that's an example of
这样的可扩展性
scalability so
排序的两倍，你知道计算机或
sort of two times you know computers or
资源让我知道你两次
resources gets me you know two times
性能和吞吐量，这是一个
performance or throughput and this is a
如果你能建立一个系统庞大锤
huge hammer if you can build a system
实际上有这种行为安室奈美惠
that actually has this behavior Namie
如果你加多少
that if you increase the number of
你把这个问题由计算机
computers you throw at the problem by
有些因素你会得到更多的因素
some factor you get that factor more
吞吐量更多表现出来的
throughput more performance out of the
系统，这是一个巨大的胜利，因为你可以
system that's a huge win because you can
买只用钱权计算机
buy computers with just money right
而如果为了得到
whereas if in order to get the
替代这是为了
alternative to this is that in order to
获得更多的性能，你必须支付
get more performance you have to pay
程序员重组软件
programmers to restructure your software
以获得更好的性能，使它
to get better performance to make it
更有效或申请某种
more efficient or to apply some sort of
专业的技术，更好的算法
specialized techniques better algorithms
或东西，如果你要付出
or something if you have to pay
程序员修复你的代码
programmers to fix your code to be
快这是一个昂贵的路要走
faster that's an expensive way to go
我们很乐意能够仅仅通过哦千
we'd love to be able just oh by thousand
计算机而不是10台计算机和
computers instead of ten computers and
获得百倍以上的吞吐量
get a hundred times more throughput
这是梦幻般的，因此这种
that's fantastic and so this sort of
可扩展性的想法是在一个巨大的想法
scalability idea is a huge idea in the
人的头上背上时，他们
backs of people's heads when they're
像建设的东西像大网站
like building things like big websites
运行的是你知道建筑全
that run on are you know building full
电脑如果建筑物充满
of computers if the building full of
电脑是那里得到了几分
computers is there to get a sort of
相应的性能量，但
corresponding amount of performance but
你必须小心设计
you have to be careful about the design
实际上为了获取
in order to actually get that
性能如此频繁的方式，这看起来
performance so often the way this looks
当我们看图表或我
when we're looking at diagrams or I'm
在这个过程中写图是
writing diagrams in this course is that
我不是假设我们正在构建一个
I'm not supposing we're building a
网站通常你可能有一个
website ordinarily you might have a
网站，你知道有一个HTTP服务器
website that you know has a HTTP server
比方说，它有一些类型的用户
let's say it has some types of users
许多Web浏览器和他们聊到网络
many web browsers and they talk to a web
服务器上运行Python或PHP或什么
server running Python or PHP or whatever
这类Web服务器和Web服务器
sort of web server and the web server
会谈某种数据库
talks to some kind of database
你知道当你有一个或两个用户
you know when you have one or two users
你可以有一个计算机运行
you can just have one computer running
两者也许用于Web的计算机
both and maybe a computer for the web
服务器从数据库的计算机
server and a computer from the database
但也许一下子你真的
but maybe all of a sudden you get really
适当的流行，你会起来
proper popular and you'll be up and
你已经知道你有1亿人的标志
you've you know 100 million people sign
你的服务ID怎么你怎么做你
up your service ID how do you how do you
解决您的C-肯定它支持
fix your c-certainly can it support
数以百万计的人在一台计算机上
millions of people on a single computer
通过非常小心除外
except by extremely careful
劳动密集型的优化，但你
labor-intensive optimization but you
没有时间所以通常的办法
don't have time for so typically the way
你要速度的东西了
you're going to speed things up the
你做的第一件事就是买多网
first thing you do is buy more web
服务器和刚刚拆分用户，以便
servers and just split the user so that
你知道如何少数用户或一些分数
you know how few users or some fraction
用户去到Web服务器1，
the user go to a web server 1 and the
另一半，你将它们发送到Web服务器
other half you send them to a web server
2，因为也许你正在构建我
2 and because maybe you're building I
不知道是什么reddit的什么
don't know what reddit or something
所有的用户需要看到相同的
where all the users need to see the same
数据最终你把所有的网页
data ultimately you have all the web
服务器聊到后端，你可以
servers talk to the backend and you can
不断增加的Web服务器很长一段
keep on adding web servers for a long
这里所以这个时候的一种方式
time here and so this is a way of
越来越平行加快在网络上
getting parallel speed up on the web
你知道，如果你正在运行的服务器代码
server code you know if you're running
PHP或者Python，也许它不是太
PHP or Python maybe it's not too
高效只要每一个人网页
efficient as long as each individual web
服务器不放在负载太大
server doesn't put too much load on the
数据库可以添加很多web
database you can add a lot of web
你之前服务器遇到问题，但
servers before you run into problems but
这种可扩展性是很少
this kind of scalability is rarely
无限遗憾的是肯定不会
infinite unfortunately certainly not
没有严肃的思考还等什么
without serious thought and so what
倾向于与这些系统发生的是
tends to happen with these systems is
在某个点之后，你有10个或
that at some point after you have 10 or
20或100的Web服务器都在谈论到
20 or 100 web servers all talking to the
现在同一个数据库中所有的突然
same database now all of a sudden the
启动数据库是一个瓶颈，
database starts to be a bottleneck and
添加更多的Web服务器不再帮助
adding more web servers no longer helps
所以这是罕见的，你得到满量程
so it's rare that you get full scale
能力排序的无限数量的
ability to sort of infinite numbers of
将计算机添加无限数量
adding infinite numbers of computers
某些时候，你气跑了，因为
some point you run out of gas because
这个地方在其中添加更多
the place at which you are adding more
计算机是不再是瓶颈
computers is no longer the bottleneck by
有很多很多的Web服务器，我们
having lots and lots of web servers we
基本上移动瓶颈
basically moved the bottleneck
我认为这是限制从性能
I think it's limiting performance from
web服务器到数据库中，并在
the web servers to the database and at
这一点其实你几乎肯定
this point actually you almost certainly
必须做一些设计工作，因为
have to do a bit of design work because
这是罕见的，你可以
it's rare that you can
有采取任何直接的方法
there's any straightforward way to take
一个单一的数据库和排序的重构
a single database and sort of refactor
用它的东西，或者你可以采取数据
things with it or you can take data
八九不离十在一个单一的数据库重构
sorta in a single database and refactor
它，所以它的分裂在多个数据库
it so it's split over multiple databases
但通常的工作相当数量的和
but it's often a fair amount of work and
因为它是尴尬的，但很多人
because it's awkward but people many
人们真正需要做到这一点我们
people actually need to do this we're
会看到很多的例子在这
gonna see a lot of examples in this
当然，其中分布式系统
course in which the distributed system
人们正在谈论的是一个存储
people are talking about is a storage
系统因为作者正在运行
system because the authors were running
你知道的东西像一个大网站
you know something like a big website
单个数据库上运行的气体从
that ran out of gas on a single database
或存储服务器反正所以
or storage servers anyway so the
可扩展性的故事是我们所爱的构建
scalability story is we love to build
如此规模这样，但你知道系统
systems that scale this way but you know
很难使其或者需要关闭工作
it's hard to make it or takes work off
和设计工作，以推动这一想法
and design work to push this idea
无限远的确定，所以另一个大话题
infinitely far ok so another big topic
自带了很多的容错
that comes up a lot is fault tolerance
如果您正在构建一个系统
if you're building a system with a
在这台计算机以及单
single computer in it well a single
电脑经常可以保持好几年
computer often can stay up for years
像我有服务器在我的办公室里
like I have servers in my office that
已经好几年没有崩溃
have been up for years without crashing
您知道计算机是相当可靠
you know the computer is pretty reliable
操作系统可靠
the operating systems reliable
显然在我的建筑功率
apparently the power in my building is
相当可靠所以它的情况并不少见
pretty reliable so it's not uncommon to
有单台计算机，它只是一个用于
have single computers it's just a for
数量惊人的时间不过如果你是
amazing amount of time however if you're
建筑系统出千的
building systems out of thousands of
电脑那么即使每台计算机都可以
computers then even if each computer can
预计熬夜与一一年
be expected to stay up for a year with a
成千上万的计算机，这意味着你
thousand computers that means you're
将有像约三个电脑
going to have like about three computer
每天失败在您所设定的一个
failures per day in your set of a
千元电脑，所以解决大
thousand computers so solving big
大的分布式系统问题
problems with big distributed systems
原来那种非常罕见的容错
turns sort of very rare fault tolerance
非常现实的故障非常罕见故障
very real failure very rare failure
问题到故障的问题，
problems into failure problems that
刚刚发生的所有的时间在一个系统
happen just all the time in a system
有成千上万的计算机上有几乎
with a thousand computers there's almost
当然总有一些事情打破它
certainly always something broken it's
总有一些计算机要么
always some computer that's either
崩溃或神秘你知道运行
crashed or mysteriously you know running
不正确或慢或做了错误的
incorrectly or slowly or doing the wrong
事情也许有一些片的
thing or maybe there's some piece of the
网络我们有一千台计算机
network with a thousand computers we got
很多网线和大量的
a lot of network cables and a lot of
网络交换机等你知道有
network switches and so you know there's
总有一些网线，有人
always some network cable that somebody
踩到和不可靠性是或
stepped on and is unreliability or
网络电缆脱落的还是一些
network cable that fell out or some
网络，这其风扇损坏和
networks which whose fan is broken and
开关过热和失败的有
the switch overheated and failed there's
总有一些小问题在某处
always some little problem somewhere in
您的建筑尺寸分布式系统
your building sized distributed system
这么大的规模原来的问题，从非常
so big scale turns problems from very
你真的不必罕见事件
rare events you really don't have to
担心这么多逼到不变
worry about that much into just constant
问题这意味着失败有
problems that means the failure has to
真或响应掩蔽
be really or the response the masking of
故障继续运行，没有能力
failures the ability to proceed without
失败只是有被内置到
failures just has to be built into the
设计，因为总是有故障
design because there's always failures
你知道它的部分建筑你的
and you know it's part of building you
知道方便抽象
know convenient abstractions for
我们真正需要的应用程序的程序员
application programmers we really need
那可是要能够建立
that but to be able to build
基础设施，尽可能多地
infrastructure that as much as possible
隐藏应用的故障
hides the failures from application
程序员或口罩他们什么
programmers or masks them or something
让每一个应用程序的程序员
so that every application programmer
不必有一个完整的
doesn't have to have a complete
所有不同复杂的故事
complicated story for all the different
各种可能发生的有故障
kinds of failures that can occur there's
一堆不同的概念，你
a bunch of different notions that you
可以有意味着什么是错
can have about what it means to be fault
沉得住气多一点，但你
tolerant about a little more but you
确切地知道我们所说的，我们会意味着
know exactly what we mean by that we'll
看到很多很多不同口味的
see a lot of a lot of different flavors
但更常见的想法中看到
but among the more common ideas you see
一个是可用性，所以你知道一些
one is availability so you know some
系统被设计成在某些
systems are designed so that under some
一种特定类型的故障并非全部
kind certain kinds of failures not all
失败，但某些种类的故障
failures but certain kinds of failures
该系统将继续运行，尽管
the system will keep operating despite
失败的同时提供你知道
the failure while providing you know
完好的服务相同类型的
undamaged service the same kind of
它会提供即使服务
service it would have provided even if
曾有过没有失败这样一些
there had been no failure so some
系统是在这个意义上，现有
systems are available in that sense that
起来，起来，你知道，所以如果你建立一个
up and up you know so if you build a
也许有两个复制服务
replicated service that maybe has two
你知道其中一个副本复印件
copies you know one of the replicas
副本服务器失败，也许失败
replica servers fail fails maybe the
其他服务器可以继续运行
other server can continue operating
他们都失败，当然你也贵不了
they both fail of course you can't you
知道你不能保证可用性
know you can't promise availability in
这种情况下，通常使现有系统
that case so available systems usually
说好了在某些集的失败
say well under certain set of failures
我们将继续提供
we're going to continue providing
服务我们将提供更多
service we're going to be available more
失败不是发生也不会
failures than that occur it won't be
提供了
available anymore
另一种容错的你
another kind of fault tolerance you
也许你可能有或除
might you might have or in addition to
可用性或通过本身作为
availability or by itself as
可恢复性和这意味着
recoverability and what this means is
如果出现错误的可能
that if something goes wrong maybe the
服务将停止工作，这是
service will stop working that it is
它会简单地停止响应请求
it'll simply stop responding to requests
它会等待有人来
and it will wait for someone to come
沿和修理或什么地方出了错
along and repair or whatever went wrong
但修复后发生的系统
but after the repair occurs the system
将能够继续仿佛什么都没有
will be able to continue as if nothing
坏出了错权，所以这是排序
bad had gone wrong right so this is sort
比较弱的要求
of a weaker requirement than
可用性，因为在这里我们不
availability because here we're not
打算做任何事情，而同时
going to do anything while while the
失败来，直到发生故障的组件
failed come until the failed component
已经修复，但事实是，我们
has been repaired but the fact that we
最多可以得到再次得到去没有你
can get up get going again without you
知道但没有正确的任何损失
know but without any loss of correctness
仍然是一个显著要求它
is still a significant requirement it
意味着你知道可恢复系统
means you know recoverable systems
通常需要做的事情一样保存
typically need to do things like save
在磁盘上或一些他们的最新日期
their latest date on disk or something
在那里他们可以找回来
where they can get it back
你知道电力恢复后，向上
you know after the power comes back up
甚至在现有系统中
and even among available systems in
为了使系统能够在实际有用
order for a system to be useful in real
寿命通常可用什么方式
life usually what the way available
系统SPECT是，他们
systems are SPECT is that they're
可用，直到一些数量的故障
available until some number of failures
发生，如果太多的失败有
have happened if too many failures have
正巧一个可用的系统将停止
happened an available system will stop
工作或你知道会停止响应
working or you know will stop responding
在所有但当足够的事情已经
at all but when enough things have been
修好后它会继续工作这么
repaired it'll continue operating so a
好可用的系统将整理BE的
good available system will sort of be
在敏感可恢复以及
recoverable as well in a sensitive to
许多发生故障
many failures occur
它会停止接听，但随后会
it'll stop answering but then will
正确之后，所以这是继续
continue correctly after that so this is
我们热爱 - 这就是我们很乐意
what we love - this is what we'd love to
获得最大的锤子我们会看到
obtain the biggest hammer what we'll see
一些方法来解决这些
a number of approaches to solving these
问题没什么排序
problems there's really sort of
事情是最重要的工具
things that are the most important tools
我们在这个部门是一个
we have in this department one is
非易失性存储，让你知道
non-volatile storage so that you know
东西崩溃电源故障或任何
something crash power fails or whatever
有一个广泛的建设停电我们
there's a building wide power failure we
可以使用非易失性存储器它像
can use non-volatile store it's like
硬盘驱动器或闪存或固态
hard drives or flash or solid-state
驱动器或东西排序商店A
drives or something to sort of store a
检查点或日志的状态
check point or a log of the state of a
系统，然后当动力来自
system and then when the power comes
备份或某人修理我们的力量
back up or somebody repairs our power
供应商注意什么，我们就可以
suppliers notice what we'll be able to
请阅读我们的最新状态关闭硬盘驱动器
read our latest state off the hard drive
并从那里这么这么一个工具继续
and continue from there so so one tool
是那种非易失性存储器和所述
is sort of non-volatile storage and the
非易失性存储管理刚
management of non-volatile storage just
宁来了很多，因为非易失性
Ning comes up a lot because non-volatile
存储往往是昂贵的更新
storage tends to be expensive to update
所以一个巨大的那种量
and so a huge amount of the sort of
建筑排序的基本事实
nitty-gritty of building sort of
高性能容错系统
high-performance fault-tolerant systems
是你知道聪明的方式，以避免
is in you know clever ways to avoid
具有写入非易失性存储
having to write the non-volatile storage
太多昔日和今日连
too much in the old days and even today
你知道什么是写非易失性
you know what writing non-volatile
存储意味着在动盘臂和
storage meant was moving a disk arm and
等待盘片旋转
waiting for a disk platter to rotate
这两者都是极其缓慢上
both of which are agonizingly slow on
你的规模知道3千兆赫
the scale of you know three gigahertz
微处理器的好东西像Flash
microprocessors good things like flash
生活是一个相当好一点，但仍然
life is quite a bit better but still
需要大量的思想得到很好的
requires a lot of thought to get good
表现出和其他大
performance out of and the other big
工具，我们有容错性
tool we have for fault tolerance is
复制和管理
replication and the management of
复制副本是有点棘手的您
replicated copies is sort of tricky you
知道那种潜伏在问题
know that sort of he problem lurking in
任何复制的系统，我们有两个
any replicated system where we have two
每一个假想相同的服务器
servers each with a supposedly identical
系统状态的关键问题的复制
copy of the system state the key problem
即出现始终是两个
that comes up is always that the two
副本一不小心就会飘出来
replicas will accidentally drift out of
同步和将不再是复制权
sync and will stop being replicas right
而这仅仅是你知道与背部
and this is just you know with the back
每次的设计，我们要看到的
of the every design that we're gonna see
使用复制来获得故障
for using replication to get fault
宽容和实验室 - 很多 - 你所有
tolerance and lab - a lot - you're all
关于管理的管理
about management management of
容错复制拷贝
replicated copies for fault tolerance
因为你会看到它的相当复杂的一个
as you'll see it's pretty complex a
最后一个主题最终跨领域的主题是
final topic final cross-cutting topic is
一致性，所以它的一个例子是我
consistency so it's an example of what I
通过一致性的意思，以为我们是
mean by consistency supposing we're
构建分布式存储系统
building a distributed storage system
这是一个键/值服务，所以它只是
and it's a key/value service so it just
支持两种操作也许有一个
supports two operations maybe there's a
放置操作，你给它一个键，
put operation and you give it a key and
一个值，该存储系统排序
a value and that the storage system sort
储物箱远离下的值作为的
of stashes away the value under as the
此键的值可以保持它只是一个
value for this key maintains it's just a
键和值，然后大表
big table of keys and values and then
有一个很好的操作，你的客户
there's a good operation you the client
发送一条键和存储服务
sends it a key and the storage service
应该知道响应与
is supposed to you know respond with the
它保存价值的价值
value of the value it has stored for
该键右侧，这是一种很好的
that key right and this is kind of good
当我想不出别的如
when I can't think of anything else as
分布式系统的一个例子的所有
an example of a distributed system all
哦不键值服务
Oh without key value services and
他们他们只是非常有用的权利
they're very useful right they're just
排序一种基本的简单的
sort of a kind of fundamental simple
存储系统的版本，所以当然
version of a storage system so of course
如果你是一个应用程序的程序员很
if you're an application programmer it's
有益的，如果这两个操作样的
helpful if these two operations kind of
重视他们，你的意思
have meanings attached to them that you
可以去看看手册和说明书
can go look in the manual and the manual
说，你知道它是什么意思
says you know what it what it means what
你会回来，如果你打电话得到正确的
you'll get back if you call get right
和排序意味着什么给你
and sort of what it means for you to
呼叫被置于没事所以它立即使
call put all right so it's immediate so
某种规范的，因为他们是什么意思
some sort of spec for what they meant
否则就像谁知道你怎么
otherwise like who knows how can you
可能写没有一个应用程序
possibly write an application without a
是什么把得到的是描述
description of what putting get are
应该做的，这是的话题
supposed to do and this is the topic of
一致性和为什么它的原因
consistency and the reason why it's
在分布式系统中有趣的是
interesting in distributed systems is
这两个性能和故障
that both for performance and for fault
宽容的原因容错原因
tolerant reasons fault tolerance reason
我们经常的多个副本
we often have more than one copy of the
数据左右浮动，所以你在知道
data floating around so you know in a
非分布式系统，你只
non distributed system where you just
有一个表中的单个服务器
have a single server with a single table
有经常虽然不总是但
there's often although not always but
经常有像相对不
there's often like relatively no
含糊不清什么布丁GET可能
ambiguity about what pudding get could
可能平均权
possibly mean right in
到ative李你知道什么把手段是
to ative Lee you know what put means is
更新表，并得到什么手段
update the table and what get means is
只是让我一个储存在版本
just get me the version that's stored in
但其在分布式表
the table which but in a distributed
系统中有多个副本
system where there's more than one copy
在由于在复制或数据
in the data due to replication or
缓存或谁知道有可能是
caching or who knows what there may be
许多不同版本的这个关键的
lots of different versions of this key
值对左右浮动一样，如果一个
value pair floating around like if one
的副本，你知道，如果假设
of the replicas you know if supposing
一些客户发出看跌期权，你知道
some client issues a put and you know
还有的服务器的两个副本等等
there's two copies of the the server so
他们都有一个键值右表
they both have a key value table right
也许关键一个有值20上
and maybe key one has value twenty on
他们两个，然后一些客户端问题
both of them and then some client issues
认沽不错，我们有客户在这里和
a put nice we have client over here and
它会发送它要更新认沽
it's gonna send a put it wants to update
一个值是21全部
the value of one to be twenty-one all
右也许它计算的东西，在这
right maybe it's counting stuff in this
键值服务器，以便将与主要看跌
key value server so sends a put with key
一个和值21将其发送到
one and value twenty one it sends it to
第一个服务器，它是关于送
the first server and it's about to send
你知道同放要更新
the same put you know wants to update
这两个副本的权利也让他们在同步
both copies right it keeps them in sync
它是关于发送此看跌，但只是
it's about to send this put but just
之前将其发送到付诸第二
before it sends to put to the second
服务器崩溃我电源故障或错误的
server crashes I power failure or bug an
所以现在的操作系统或东西
operating system or something so now the
状态留在伤心地是，我们派出
state were left in sadly is that we sent
该看跌期权的，所以我们已经更新了一个
this put and so we've updated one of the
两个副本没有值20
two replicas didn't have value twenty
之一，但其他的人仍然具有二十
one but the other ones still with twenty
现在有人走来，并与读取
now somebody comes along and reads with
一大家子，他们可能会得到他们想要
a get and they might get they want to
阅读与关键一个关联的值
read the value associated with key one
他们可能会得到21或者他们可能
they might get twenty one or they might
这取决于他们要向谁倾诉得到20
get twenty depending on who they talk to
即使规则是你总是说话
and even if the rule is you always talk
顶端服务器首先，如果你是
to the top server first if you're
建立一个容错系统
building a fault-tolerant system the
实际的规则必须是哦，你去跟
actual rule has to be oh you talk to the
顶级服务器首先，除非它是失败的
top server first unless it's failed in
你跟底部的服务器这种情况下，
which case you talk to the bottom server
所以哪天方式任你风险暴露
so either way someday you risk exposing
数据的一些陈旧的这个副本
this stale copy of the data to some
将来再次它可能是很多变
future again it could be that many gets
获得更新的21，然后像
get the updated twenty one and then like
下周一下子有些人会
next week all of a sudden some get
国债收益率你知道的一个星期旧副本
yields you know a week old copy of the
数据，这样不是很一致
data so that's not very consistent
右所以要想但你知道它的
right so in order but you know it's the
这样的事情可能发生的权利
kind of thing that could happen right
我们不小心，所以你知道我们需要
we're not careful so you know we need to
有我们需要真正写下
have we need to actually write down what
该规则将是关于puts和
the rules are going to be about puts and
被赋予由于这种危险
gets given this danger of due to
复制和原来有
replication and it turns out there's
许多不同的定义，你可以有
many different definitions you can have
一致性的，你知道有很多是
of consistency you know many of them are
它们的相对简单的多
relatively straightforward many of them
听起来很好，我得到的收益率，你
sound like well I get yields the you
知道大多数最近值看跌期权
know value put by the most recently
完成把所有的权利，这样的
completed put all right so that's
通常被称为强一致性，
usually called strong consistency it
事实证明也这是构建非常有用
turns out also it's very useful to build
有弱得多系统
systems that have much weaker
一致性有比如不
consistency there for example do not
就像一个GET保证任何看到
guarantee anything like a get sees the
由最近放写入值和
value written by the most recent put and
之所以这么有强烈的存在
the reason so there's there strongly
他们通常有一致的系统
consistent systems they usually have
一些版本，被看到最近
some version that gets seen most recent
看跌期权虽然你必须有很多
puts although you have to there's a lot
的细节工作，在那里也
of details to work out there's also
每周一致许多种类的味道
weekly consistent many sort of flavors
不每周一致系统
of weekly consistent systems that do not
作出任何保证你知道
make any such guarantee that you know
可以保证你离你知道，如果
may guarantee well you're you know if
有人不看跌，那么你可能看不到
someone does a put then you may not see
认沽您可能会看到旧值即
the put you may see old values that
没有被放了一个更新
weren't updated by the put for an
时间无限量可能与
unbounded amount of time maybe and the
之所以被人们非常感兴趣
reason for people being very interested
在小麦一致性方案是
in wheat consistency schemes is that
即具有雷扎克强一致性
strong consistency that is having Rezac
蔡承租人保证看到的
Chua lessee be guaranteed to see the
最近权，这是一个非常
most recent right that's a very
昂贵的规范来实现的原因是什么
expensive spec to implement because what
它的意思是几乎可以肯定的是你
it means is almost certainly that you
必须要有人做了很多的
have to somebody has to do a lot of
为了通信实际
communication in order to actually
落实强一些概念
implement some notion of strong
一致性，如果您有多个副本
consistency if you have multiple copies
它意味着，或者写入器或
it means that either the writer or the
读者也许既有咨询
reader or maybe both has to consult
每个副本像在这种情况下，你
every copy like in this case where you
知道也许客户端崩溃留下一个
know maybe a client crash left one
更新但如果我们想其他
updated but not the other if we wanted
落实强
to implement strong
西瑟顿从中看到，也许一个简单的方法
Sisseton see in them maybe a simple way
在这个系统中，我们不得不读者阅读
in this system we'd have readers read
副本，或者如果双方有更多的
both of the copies or if there's more
比一个复制的所有副本，并使用
than one copy all the copies and use the
最近写入的价值，他们
most recently written value that they
发现但这是昂贵的，这是一个很大
find but that's expensive that's a lot
闲聊中读取一个值，所以在
of chitchat to read one value so in
为了尽可能避免通信
order to avoid communication as much as
可能特别是如果副本是
possible particularly if replicas are
远离人们建立弱电系统是
far away people build weak systems that
实际上可能允许的读取过时
might actually allow the stale read of
在这种情况下，虽然旧的价值
an old value in this case although
有附着往往更语义
there's often more semantics attached to
即尽量使这些薄弱方案
that to try to make these weak schemes
更有用，我们这个通信
more useful and we're this communication
问题你知道强一致性
problem you know strong consistency
需要昂贵的通信，其中
requiring expensive communication where
这真的跑你陷入困境IS
this really runs you into trouble is
如果我们使用复制功能
that if we're using replication for
容错那么我们真正想要的
fault tolerance then we really want the
复制品有独立的失败
replicas to have independent failure
概率是不相关的故障
probability to have uncorrelated failure
因此，例如，把双方的
so for example putting both of the
在同伊拉克在我们数据的副本
replicas of our data in the same iraq in
同一机房它可能是一个
the same machine room it's probably a
非常糟糕的主意
really bad idea
因为如果有人绊倒电源
because if someone trips over the power
电缆到机架我们两个副本
cable to that rack both of our copies of
我们的数据会死，因为
our data are going to die because
他们都连接到相同的电源
they're both attached to the same power
电缆在同一机架所以在搜索
cable in the same rack so in the search
制作副本作为独立
for making replicas as independent and
故障尽可能以获得
failure as possible in order to get
体面的容错能力的人会爱
decent fault tolerance people would love
把不同的副本相距甚远
to put different replicas as far apart
在不同的城市或可能喜欢
as possible like in different cities or
也许在大陆的两侧
maybe on opposite sides of the continent
这样的地震，摧毁一个数据
so an earthquake that destroys one data
中心将极不可能
center will be extremely unlikely to
也会破坏其他数据中心
also destroy the other data center that
与其他副本，你知道的，所以我们很乐意
as the other copy you know so we'd love
要能做到这一点，如果你这样做
to be able to do that if you do that
那么另一份是千
then the other copy is thousands of
英里远和的速率光
miles away and the rate at which light
行进装置，它可能需要在
travels means that it may take on the
毫秒或几十秒的顺序
order of milliseconds or tens of
毫秒传送到数据
milliseconds to communicate to a data
为了整个非洲大陆的中心，
center across the continent in order to
更新数据等其他副本
update the other copy of the data and so
这使得该通信
that makes this the communication
需要良好的强一致性
required for strong consistency for good
一致性可能极其
consistency potentially extremely
昂贵的像你想要做的每一次
expensive like every time you want to do
这些放歌剧之一
one of these put opera
也许这也取决于你如何
or maybe again depending on how you
实现它，你可能会坐在那里
implement it you might have to sit there
等待像10或20或30
waiting for like 10 or 20 or 30
毫秒以谈话既
milliseconds in order to talk to both
数据的副本，以确保
copies of the data to ensure that
他们俩都更新或或托运
they're both updated or or both checked
找到最新的副本，以及
to find the latest copy and that
巨大的代价权，这是10或
tremendous expense right this is 10 or
20或30毫秒上的机器，
20 or 30 milliseconds on machines that
毕竟，我会执行像一个十亿
after all I'll execute like a billion
条指令每秒所以我们浪费
instructions per second so we're wasting
很多潜在的指令，而我们
a lot of potential instructions while we
等待的人经常去弱得多系统
wait people often go much weaker systems
你被允许只更新
you're allowed to only update the
最近的复制你只是咨询
nearest copy you're only consulted
最近的复制我的意思是有一个巨大的排序
nearest copy I mean there's a huge sort
学术和现实世界中的量
of amount of academic and real-world
如何组织薄弱的研究
research on how to structure weak
一致性保证所以他们
consistency guarantees so they're
真正有用的应用程序，以及如何
actually useful to applications and how
利用这些优势，以
to take advantage of them in order to
实际上得到高性能这么好吗
actually get high performance alright so
这是的闪电预览
that's a lightning preview of the
在使用过程中的技术思路任何
technical ideas in the course any
关于这个问题，我开始之前
questions about this before I start
谈及MapReduce的我想没事
talking about MapReduce all right I want
要切换到地图减少，这是一个排序
to switch to Map Reduce that's a sort of
详细的案例研究，实际上是
detailed case study that's actually
要说明大部分意见
going to illustrate most of the ideas
我们已经现在这里所说的
that we've been talking about here now
产生本来是一个系统
produces a system that was originally
设计和建造，并通过谷歌我用
designed and built and used by Google I
认为纸的历史可以追溯到2004年
think the paper dates back to 2004 the
他们面临的问题是，
problem they were faced with was that
他们上运行庞大的计算
they were running huge computations on
TB的和类似的数据的TB的
terabytes and terabytes of data like
创建所有内容的索引
creating an index of all of the content
网页或分析的链接
of the web or analyzing the link
整个网络的，以便结构，以
structure of the entire web in order to
找出最重要的网页或
identify the most important pages or the
最权威的网页，你知道
most authoritative pages as you know the
整个网络就是在那些日子里，甚至
whole web is what's even in those days
几十数据构建指数的TB的
tens of terabytes of data building index
网络的基本上等同于一个
of the web is basically equivalent to a
排序运行排序整个数据
sort running sort of the entire data
那种你知道那些喜欢合理
sort you know ones like reasonably
价格昂贵，在其上运行排序
expensive and to run a sort on the
整个内容我去过的方式
entire content to the way I've been a
单台计算机
single computer
多久会采取，但你知道
how long would have taken but you know
这是周或数月或数年或
it's weeks or months or years or
事情因此谷歌的时间为
something so Google the time was
不顾一切地能够运行巨人
desperate to be able to run giant
对数以千计的巨型数据计算
computations on giant data on thousands
为了电脑的
of computers in order that the
计算可以快速地完成它的
computations could finish rapidly it's
值得给他们买很多
worth it to them to buy lots of
电脑让他们的工程师
computers so that their engineers
就不必花费大量的时间
wouldn't have to spend a lot of time
读报纸什么的
reading the newspaper or something
等待他们的大计算作业
waiting for their big compute jobs to
光洁度等一会儿他们有
finish and so for a while they had their
聪明的工程师或排序手写的你
clever engineer or sort of handwrite you
知道，如果你需要写一个网页
know if you needed to write a web
索引或某种林肯支出的一
indexer or some sort of Lincoln outlay a
眨眼分析工具，你知道谷歌
blink analysis tool you know Google
买了台电脑，他们说这里
bought the computers and they say here
你知道工程师们写，但从来没有
engineers you know do write but never
任何软件，你喜欢这些
whatever software you like on these
电脑，你知道他们会
computers and you know they would
费力LY写的那种一次性的
laborious ly write the sort of one-off
手动咬伤软件采取
manually bitten software to take
任何问题，他们正在上
whatever problem they were working on
所以以某种方式外包出去了很多
and so to somehow farm it out to a lot
计算机和组织
of computers and organize that
计算并得到，如果你的数据备份
computation and get the data back if you
只雇佣谁是技术熟练的工程师
only hire engineers who are skilled
分布式系统的专家也许这就是
distributed systems experts maybe that's
OK，虽然即使这样，它可能是很
ok although even then it's probably very
浪费的工程设计工作，但他们的
wasteful of engineering effort but they
想雇用谁是熟练的人
wanted to hire people who were skilled
别的东西，而不一定
at something else and not necessarily
工程师谁想要把所有的
engineers who wanted to spend all their
时间编写分布式系统软件
time writing distributed system software
所以他们真正需要的某种
so they really needed some kind of
框架，可以很容易地
framework that would make it easy to
只是他们的工程师写的那种
just have their engineers write the kind
他们想要的任何分析的胆量
of guts of whatever analysis they wanted
做这样的排序算法或网页
to do like the sort algorithm or a web
指数或链接分析仪或任何刚
index or link analyzer or whatever just
编写应用程序的胆量和
write the guts of that application and
不能够在成千上万的运行
not be able to run it on a thousands of
电脑而不必担心
computers without worrying about the
如何在传播工作细节
details of how to spread the work over
在数千台电脑如何
the thousands of computers how to
组织任何数据移动是
organize whatever data movement was
需要如何应对不可避免的
required how to cope with the inevitable
失败使他们在寻找一个
failures so they were looking for a
框架，可以很容易的
framework that would make it easy for
非专家能够写和
non specialists to be able to write and
运行大型分布式计算和
run giant distributed computations and
所以，这就是MapReduce的是所有关于
so that's what MapReduce is all about
而这个想法是，程序员只
and the idea is that the programmer just
编写应用程序设计师
write the application designer
这种分布式计算的消费
consumer of this distributed computation
我只能够写一个简单的地图
I'm just be able to write a simple map
功能和简单的功能降低
function and a simple reduce function
不知道任何有关
that don't know anything about
分布和MapReduce框架
distribution and the MapReduce framework
会照顾一切，这样的
would take care of everything else so an
MapReduce的的是如何抽象什么看法
abstract view of how what MapReduce is
最多是它开始通过假设
up to is it starts by assuming that
有一些输入和输入
there's some input and the input is
分裂成一些一大堆
split up into some a whole bunch of
不同的文件或数据块以某种方式使
different files or chunks in some way so
我们想象没有啊，你知道
we're imagining that no yeah you know
输入文件中的一个，并把文件中的两个等你
input file one and put file two etc you
知道这些投入也许你知道网络
know these inputs are maybe you know web
页从网上或多个爬行
pages crawled from the web or more
可能有点包含大文件
likely sort of big files that contain
许多网站每个都包含许多网络
many web each of which contains many web
文件从网页抓取所有权利，
files crawl from the web all right and
路的Map Reduce
the way Map Reduce
开始是你找到的地图
starts is that you're to find a map
功能和MapReduce的框架
function and the MapReduce framework is
要对每一个运行的地图功能
gonna run your map function on each of
输入文件，当然你可以
the input files and of course you can
看到这里有一些明显的
see here there's some obvious
并行提供可以运行地图
parallelism available can run the maps
在平行所以每个地图的
in parallel so the each of these map
功能只是看起来这个输入和
functions only looks as this input and
产生输出的输出，一个地图
produces output the output that a map
需要函数，以产生一个
function is required to produce is a
请列出您知道它需要一个文件作为输入
list you know it takes a file as input
而文件的某些部分
and the file is some fraction of the
输入数据和它产生密钥的列表
input data and it produces a list of key
值对作为输出的映射函数
value pairs as output the map function
所以例如，让我们假设我们
and so for example let's suppose we're
写一个最简单的MapReduce的
writing the simplest possible MapReduce
例如字数MapReduce工作目标
example a word count MapReduce job goal
是计算出现的次数
is to count the number of occurrences of
每个字让你的地图功能的威力
each word so your map function might
发射键值对其中键是
emit key value pairs where the key is
字和值仅仅是一个如此
the word and the value is just one so
对于位于C每一个字所以那么这个地图
for every word at C so then this map
函数将分割输入成
function will split the input up into
单词或到处ditzies
words or everywhere ditzies
它发出这个词的关键和1作为
it emits that word as the key and 1 as
值，然后后来将计
the value and then later on will count
起来以获得所有的人
up all those ones in order to get the
最终的输出，让你知道，也许输入1
final output so you know maybe input 1
有单词
has the word
一个在它和它等等的字B
a in it and the word B in it and so the
在地图将要产生的输出是
output the map is going to produce is
也许键输入值一个键B值一个
key a value one key B value one maybe
第二不通信看到一个文件
the second not communication sees a file
该中有一个B和没有别的等等
that has a B in it and nothing else so
这将可能实现输出B1
it's going to implement output b1 maybe
此第三输入具有A在它和C
this third input has an A in it and a C
在好吗，所以我们运行所有这些地图
in it alright so we run all these maps
在所有输入文件，我们得到这个
on all the input files and we get this
与纸张的呼叫中间
intermediate with the paper calls
中间输出这对于每
intermediate output which is for every
映射的一组密钥值对作为输出的
map a set of key value pairs as output
然后计算的第二阶段
then the second stage of the computation
是运行减少和想法
is to run the reduces and the idea is
该MapReduce框架收集
that the MapReduce framework collects
从所有地图一起所有实例
together all instances from all maps of
每个键字所以MapReduce框架
each key word so the MapReduce framework
是要收集了所有的
is going to collect together all of the
一个就是你从每个地图每个键知道
A's you know from every map every key
值对，其关键是它的要
value pair whose key was a it's gonna
需要将它们收集齐全，并将它们交给
take collect them all and hand them to
程序员的一个打电话找
one call of the programmer to find
减少功能，那么它将会讲解
reduce function and then it's gonna take
所有B的，并收集在一起的
all the B's and collect them together of
当然，你知道需要一个真正的
course you know requires a real
集合，因为他们是不同的
collection because they were different
密钥B的实例是由产生
instances of key B were produced by
在地图上的不同的指示
different indications of map on
不同的电脑，所以我们不是在谈论
different computers so we're not talking
有关数据移动我，所以我们要去
about data movement I'm so we're gonna
收集所有B密钥，并将它们交给
collect all the B keys and hand them to
不同的电话，以减少具有所有
a different call to reduce that has all
所述乙键作为其参数和相同的
of the B keys as its arguments and same
为C所以有将是
as C so there's going to be the
MapReduce框架将安排一个
MapReduce framework will arrange for one
呼吁减少对每个密钥
call to reduce for every key that
发生于任何数学输出和
occurred in any of the math output and
你知道我们的那种愚蠢的字
you know for our sort of silly word
算上例如所有这些都降低到
count example all these reduces have to
做或其中任何一个要做的就是
do or any one of them has to do is just
数传递给它的项目数
count the number of items passed to it
甚至不必看项目
doesn't even have to look at the items
因为它知道他们每个人是
because it knows that each of them is
这个词是负责加一
the word is responsible for plus one is
值你没有看
the value you don't have to look at
比不上那些我们刚刚统计
those ones we've just count
所以这种减少会产生和
so this reduce is going to produce a and
那么它的投入计数这个降低
then the count of its inputs this reduce
它会产生相关的关键
it's going to produce the key associated
它再算上它的价值
with it and then count of its values
这也有两个，所以这是一个什么
which is also two so this is what a
典型的MapReduce工作看起来像
typical MapReduce job looks like the
高级别只是为了完整性
high level just for completeness the
还有一些术语的一点点
well some a little bit of terminology
整个计算被称为工作
the whole computation is called the job
的MapReduce任何调用被称为
anyone invocation of MapReduce is called
一个任务，使我们整个的工作，
a task so we have the entire job and
它是由一群数学任务了
it's made up of a bunch of math tasks
然后一束产生任务，以便
and then a bunch of produced tasks so
这是这个词的例子算你
it's an example for this word count you
知道地图是什么，并减少
know the what the map and reduce
功能看起来像地图
functions would look like the map
功能取入值作为密钥
function takes a key in the value as
争论现在我们谈论
arguments and now we're talking about
功能类似于写在一个普通的
functions like written in an ordinary
编程语言如C ++或Java或
programming language like C++ or Java or
谁知道所以这只是代码
who knows what so this is just code
人们一般人可以写什么
people ordinary people can write what a
地图功能的字数会做的是
map function for word count would do is
分裂的关键是程序文件名
split the the key is the file name which
通常被忽略，我们真正关心什么
typically is ignored we really care what
文件名是和V是
the file name was and the V is the
这个内容映射输入文件，因此V是
content of this maps input file so V is
你知道刚才包含所有的这段文字
you know just contains all this text
我们要拆分V输入单词，然后
we're gonna split V into words and then
每个字
for each word
我们只是要发出并发出带有两个
we're just gonna emit and emit takes two
参数手套你知道从容地图即可
arguments mitts you know calmly map can
使EMIT是由MapReduce的提供
make emit is provided by the MapReduce
框架我们得到生产我们的手EMIT
framework we get to produce we hand emit
一个关键这是字和值
a key which is the word and a value
这是一个字符串，所以这是它
which is the string one so that's it for
地图功能和字数地图
the map function and a word count map
功能和MapReduce它字面上
function and MapReduce literally it
可能是这个简单的
could be this simple
因此有某种承诺，使
so there's sort of promise to make the
而你知道这个地图功能不
and you know this map function doesn't
知道什么分发或
know anything about distribution or
多台计算机或事实上，我们需要
multiple computers or the fact we need
我们需要在整个网络中的数据
we need to move data across the network
或者谁知道
or who knows what
这是非常简单和
this is extremely straightforward and
一个字的减少功能计数
the reduce function for a word count the
减少被调用，你知道记
reduce is called with you know remember
每减少被调用排序的所有
each reduce is called with sort of all
在给定的键的情况下，
the instances of a given key on the
MapReduce框架调用减少
MapReduce framework calls reduce with
关键在于它是负责和
the key that it's responsible for and a
所有的矢量值，所述地图
vector of all the values that the maps
出品与该键相关联的
produced associated with that key the
关键是这个词的值全部为一
key is the word the values are all ones
我们不喜欢在这里对他们，我们只
we don't like here about them we only
关心他们有多少人等
care about how many they were and so
减轻了自身的省略功能
reduce has its own omit function that
只是取值被发射以所述
just takes a value to be emitted as the
作为用于此的值最终输出
final output as the value for the this
键，我们要承认的长度
key so we're gonna admit a length of
这个数组所以这也是大约为
this array so this is also about as
最简单的减少功能有是和
simplest reduce functions have are and
在地图降低即极其简单
in Map Reduce namely extremely simple
并且不需要有关故障的知识
and requiring no knowledge about fault
宽容或任何其他任何好吗
tolerance or anything else alright any
关于基本框架的问题是
questions about the basic framework yes
[音乐]
[Music]
你的意思是你可以喂的输出
you mean can you feed the output of the
异径那种哦，是哦，是的，在
reducers sort of oh yes oh yes in in in
在现实生活中所有的权利
in real life all right
在现实生活中是日常之中
in real life it is routine among
MapReduce的用户，你知道定义
MapReduce users to you know define a
MapReduce工作是采取了一些投入和
MapReduce job that took some inputs and
产生一些输出，然后有一个
produce some outputs and then have a
第二MapReduce工作你知道你是
second MapReduce job you know you're
做一些非常复杂的多级
doing some very complicated multistage
分析或迭代算法等
analysis or iterative algorithm like
的PageRank例如它是
PageRank for example which is the
算法谷歌使用排序的
algorithm Google uses to sort of
估计有重要的影响力或
estimate how important or influential
不同的网页是这是一个
different webpages are that's an
迭代算法是那种逐渐
iterative algorithm is sort of gradually
上一个答案，如果你收敛
converges on an answer and if you
在MapReduce的实现，我认为
implement in MapReduce which I think
他们本来你必须运行
they originally did you have to run the
MapReduce工作多次和
MapReduce job multiple times and the
每一个的输出是那种你知道
output of each one is sort of you know
网页使用更新的排序列表
list of webpages with an updated sort of
值或重量或重要性为每个
value or weight or importance for each
网页所以这是例行借此
webpage so it was routine to take this
输出，然后用它作为输入到
output and then use it as the input to
另一个MapReduce工作哦耶好耶
another MapReduce job oh yeah well yeah
你需要排序的一套东西了
you need to sort of set things up the
输出就需要率降低
output you need to rate the reduced
功能排序的知识
function sort of in the knowledge that
哦，我需要这是在生产数据
oh I need to produce data that's in the
格式化或作为信息所需
format or as the information required
下一个MapReduce工作我的意思是
for the next MapReduce job I mean this
实际上带来了一点点
actually brings up a little bit of a
缺点在MapReduce框架
shortcoming in the MapReduce framework
这是这是伟大的，如果你是，如果
which is it's great if you are if the
算法需要运行很容易
algorithm you need to run is easily
表达为一个数学跟此
expressible as a math followed by this
那种通过洗牌的关键数据
sort of shuffling of the data by key
随后是减少，这就是它
followed by a reduce and that's it
我的MapReduce是梦幻般的算法
my MapReduce is fantastic for algorithms
可以在形式和投我们
that can be cast in that form and we're
此外，每个地图的必须是
furthermore each of the maps has to be
完全独立的，
completely independent and
需要是纯功能性
are required to be functional pure
功能性的功能，只是看
functional functions that just look at
他们的论点，没有别的
their arguments and nothing else
你知道的就像是一个限制
you know that's like it's a restriction
而事实证明，很多人都希望
and it turns out that many people want
运行更长的管道是
to run much longer pipelines that
涉及到许许多多不同类型的
involve lots and lots of different kinds
处理与MapReduce的你
of processing and with MapReduce you
有排序凑齐一起的
have to sort of cobble that together
从多个不同的MapReduce
from multiple MapReduce distinct
MapReduce作业和更先进的系统
MapReduce jobs and more advanced systems
我们将在以后的谈
which we will talk about later in the
当然是在让你更好
course are much better at allowing you
指定的完整流水线
to specify the complete pipeline of
计算和他们会做优化
computations and they'll do optimization
你知道的框架来实现所有
you know the framework realizes all the
的东西，你必须做的，组织多
stuff you have to do and organize much
更复杂有效地优化
more complicated efficiently optimize
更复杂的计算
much more complicated computations
从程序员的角度来看它
from the programmers point of view it's
只是地图，从我们的角度减少
just about map and reduce from our point
来看这将是对
of view it's going to be about the
工作进程和劳动者服务器
worker processes and the worker servers
这是他们的MapReduce的一部分
that that are they're part of MapReduce
框架，在许多其他事情
framework that among many other things
调用地图和减少功能，使
call the map and reduce functions so
是啊，从我们的角度来看，我们不在乎
yeah from our point of view we care a
很多关于如何通过组织
lot about how this is organized by the
周围的框架，这是有点
surrounding framework this is sort of
程序员查看所有的
the programmers view with all the
分配的东西剥离出去是
distributive stuff stripped out yes
抱歉，我得再说一遍哦，你的意思是
sorry I gotta say it again oh you mean
哪里的即时数据去好了，
where does the immediate data go okay so
有两个问题一个是当你
there's two questions one is when you
调用MIT发生了什么数据和
call a MIT what happens to the data and
另一种是，其中的功能运行，从而
the other is where the functions run so
实际的答案是，首先在那里
the actual answer is that first where
东西烂有一些发言权
the stuff rotten there's a number of say
一千台服务器UM实际的右边
a thousand servers um actually the right
看看这里的是人物之一
thing to look at here is figure one in
本文在此坐在底下
the paper sitting underneath this in the
现实世界中有一些大集合
real world there's some big collection
服务器的，我们也许会打电话给他们
of servers and we'll call them maybe
工人服务器或职工和有
worker servers or workers and there's
也是一个单一的主服务器的
also a single master server that's
组织整个计算和
organizing the whole computation and
这是怎么回事上是高手
what's going on here is the master
服务器知道知道有一些
server for know knows that there's some
你知道五个输入文件的数量
number of input files you know five
千个输入文件，它在养殖场出来
thousand input files and it farms out in
地图的假期不同
vacations of map to the different
工人所以它会发送消息到
workers so it'll send a message to
工人7句话，请你跑知道
worker seven saying please run you know
在这样和 - 这样的本地图功能
this map function on such-and-such an
输入文件，然后工人功能
input file and then the worker function
这是你知道的MapReduce的一部分，
which is you know part of MapReduce and
知道所有的Map Reduce以及随后
knows all about Map Reduce well then
读取文件读取输入任何
read the file read the input whatever
无论输入文件并调用此地图
whichever input file and call this map
与文件名称值，它的功能
function with the file name value as its
论据那么工作进程
arguments then that worker process will
员工在什么它实现和
employees what implements in it and
每一次地图调用发出工作者
every time the map calls emit the worker
过程中会将该数据写入文件上
process will write this data to files on
本地磁盘，从而发生了什么地图
the local disk so what happens to map
发射是他们生产的文件
emits and is they produce files on the
映射本地工人的光盘是
map workers local discs that are
积累的所有键和值
accumulating all the keys and values
通过对工人运行的地图制作
produced by the maps run on that worker
所以在数学阶段的到底是什么
so at the end of the math phase what
我们留下的是所有这些工人
we're left with is all those worker
机，其中每个都具有的输出
machines each of which has the output of
一些什么地图都在运行
some of whatever maps were run on that
工人机那么的MapReduce
worker machine then the MapReduce
工作人员安排将数据移动到
workers arrange to move the data to
在那里将是需要的
where it's going to be needed for the
减少这么既然和你在知道
reduces so and since and a you know in a
典型的大计算你知道这
typical big computation you know this
这减少指示将需要
this reduce indication is going to need
所有地图输出
all map output that
提到键，但它要去把
mentioned the key a but it's gonna turn
出你知道这是一个简单的例子
out you know this is a simple example
但可能在一般每一张地图
but probably in general every single map
指示将产生大量的
indication will have produce lots of
按键包括键的某些实例
keys including some instances of key a
所以通常是为了之前，我们甚至可以
so typically in order before we can even
运行此功能降低映射减少
run this reduce function the MapReduce
框架是MapReduce的工作人员
framework that is the MapReduce worker
我们一千台服务器的一个运行
running on one of our thousand servers
是将不得不去跟每
is going to have to go talk to every
单以外的数千个服务器和
single other of the thousand servers and
比方说看你知道我会运行
say look you know I'm gonna run the
减少在键请看
reduce for key a please look at the
存储在中间映射输出的
intermediate map output stored in your
磁盘捞出所有实例
disk and fish out all of the instances
关键的一个，并将它们发送网络
of key a and send them over the network
我这么精简工作打算
to me so the reduce worker is going to
做到这一点它会从每一个获取
do that it's going to fetch from every
工人所有关键的实例
worker all of the instances of the key
这是负责的
that it's responsible for that the
主人告诉它要负责
master has told it to be responsible for
一旦它收集到的所有数据的
and once it's collected all of that data
然后它可以调用减少和降低
then it can call reduce and the reduce
函数本身调用减少其省略
function itself calls reduce omit which
是从它的地图，什么不同
is different from the map in it and what
降低EMIT确实是写入输出
reduces emit does is writes the output
在集群文件服务，文件
to a file in a cluster file service that
谷歌使用所以这里的东西我
Google uses so here's something I
没有提到我没有提到
haven't mentioned I haven't mentioned
其中输入和生活的地方
where the input lives and where the
输出住他们两个文件，因为
output lives they're both files because
任何一块输入我们想要的
any piece of input we want the
灵活性，能够读取任何片
flexibility to be able to read any piece
任何工人服务器意味着输入
of input on any worker server that means
我们需要某种形式的网络文件系统
we need some kind of network file system
存储输入数据等的确
to store the input data and so indeed
关于这件事情的文件名为会谈
the paper talks about this thing called
GFS或谷歌文件系统和GFS是
GFS or Google file system and GFS is a
集群文件系统和实际BFS
cluster file system and BFS actually
运行在完全相同的一组工人
runs on exactly the same set of workers
这项工作我们的服务器是运行的MapReduce
that work our servers that run MapReduce
和输入只是自动GFS
and the input GFS just automatically
当你你知道这是一个文件系统，你
when you you know it's a file system you
可以在我的文件中读取它只是
can read in my files it just
自动拆分的任何大的文件，你
automatically splits up any big file you
它存储在许多不同的服务器，并
store on it across lots of servers and
所以，如果你写64兆点字节的块
64 megabyte chunks so if you write
如果您查看已爬10 TB的
if you view of ten terabytes of crawled
网页内容，你只要写
web page contents and you just write
他们GFS甚至一个大的文件
them to GFS even as a single big file
GFS会自动拆分广阔
GFS will automatically split that vast
数据的量成64千字节
amount of data up into 64 kilobyte
块均匀地分布在所有的
chunks distributed evenly over all of
政府飞行服务队服务器这是说所有的
the GFS servers which is to say all the
服务器，谷歌已经可用，
servers that Google has available and
这是梦幻般的，这只是我们什么
that's fantastic that's just what we
如果需要我们接着要运行的MapReduce
need if we then want to run a MapReduce
作业需要整个网页抓取的作为
job that takes the entire crawled web as
输入数据已经被存储在一个
input the data is already stored in a
可以跨所有平分方式
way that split up evenly across all the
服务器，并且使得装置，地图
servers and so that means that the map
你知道工人我们要发动你
workers you know we're gonna launch you
知道如果我们有一千台服务器我们
know if we have a thousand servers we're
要发动每一千个工人地图
gonna launch a thousand map workers each
在输入数据读取一个1000和
reading one 1000s at the input data and
他们将能够阅读
they're going to be able to read the
从一千GFS并行数据
data in parallel from a thousand GFS
因此，文件服务器越来越现在巨大
file servers thus getting now tremendous
总读取吞吐量你知道读
total read throughput you know the read
通过把一个一千台服务器
through put up a thousand servers
所以这样你在想，也许，谷歌
so so are you thinking maybe that Google
其中有一组物理机器
has one set of physical machines among
GFS和一组单独的物理
GFS and a separate set of physical
机器，运行MapReduce工作好吗
machines that run MapReduce jobs okay
所以正确的问题是什么呢这
right so the question is what does this
箭头这里实际上涉及到与
arrow here actually involve and the
回答这个问题其实是有点改变
answer that actually it sort of changed
多年来谷歌的
over the years as Google's
涉及此系统，但你知道吗
involve this system but you know what
这如果我们有这些一般的情况下
this in those general case if we have
存储在一些大的网络大文件
big files stored in some big Network
文件系统一样，你知道它像GFS
file system like you know it's like GFS
有点像AFS你可能已经使用上
is a bit like AFS you might have used on
雅典娜，你去跟一些
Athena where you go talk to some
收集并通过大数据分
collection and your data split over big
集合O服务器，你必须去谈话
collection o servers you have to go talk
通过网络向这些服务器
to those servers over the network to
检索在这种情况下你的数据是什么
retrieve your data in that case what
此箭头可能代表的是元
this arrow might represent is the meta
MapReduce的工作进程已熄灭
MapReduce worker process has to go off
并通过网络交谈的
and talk across the network to the
正确的GFS服务器或也许服务器的
correct GFS server or maybe servers that
存储它的部分输入和读取
store it's part of the input and fetch
它在网络上的MapReduce的
it over the network to the MapReduce
工人机为了通过地图
worker machine in order to pass the map
而这肯定是最普遍
and that's certainly the most general
情况下，那就是最终如何
case and that was eventually how
MapReduce的实际世界工作
MapReduce actually worked in the world
本文虽然和，如果你做了
of this paper though and and if you did
那这是很多网络
that that's a lot of network
通信，你说约十
communication are you talking about ten
TB的数据，我们已经搬到10
terabytes of data and we have moved 10
在他们的数据中心千兆字节
terabytes across their data center
你知道数据中心网络
network which you know data center
网络希望每秒吉比特但
networks wanting gigabits per second but
它仍然是一个大量的时间来搬家几十
it's still a lot of time to move tens of
为了尽量TB级的数据和
terabytes of data in order to try to and
的确在本文的世界
indeed in the world of this paper in
2004年最制约瓶颈
2004 the most constraining bottleneck in
他们的MapReduce系统是网络
their MapReduce system was Network
吞吐量，因为他们上运行
throughput because they were running on
如果你有点读至于网络
a network if you sort of read as far as
评估部分其网络
the evaluation section their network
他们的网络是他们有成千上万
their network as was they had thousands
机
of machines
不管他们会收集机
whatever and they would collect machines
他们会堵塞机器，你知道
they would plug machines and you know
机器的每个机架，你知道的
each rack of machines and you know an
对于机架式以太网交换机或
Ethernet switch for that rack or
的东西，但你就知道他们都
something but then you know they all
需要相互交谈，但有
need to talk to each other but there was
路由以太网交换机，所有的
a route Ethernet switch that all of the
落基山脉的净开关交谈和
Rockies are net switches talked to and
这一次，你知道，所以如果你只是
this one and you know so if you just
挑选一些地图，减少工人和一些政府飞行服务队
pick some Map Reduce worker and some GFS
服务器要知道机会是至少
server you know chances are at least
一半的时间之间的通信
half the time the communication between
他们必须通过这一个
them has to pass through this one
不会切换其途径有哪些
wouldn't switch their routes which had
只有总吞吐量的一定量
only some amount of total throughput
我忘了你知道的一些数
which I forget you know some number of
吉比特每秒，我忘记了
gigabits per second and I forget the
数字很​​好，但，当我做除法
number well but when I did the division
被划分高达总
that is divided up to the total
吞吐量路由可用其
throughput available in the routes which
由大约2000服务器，他们
by the roughly 2000 servers that they
在论文的实验我用什么
used in the papers experiments what I
得到的是那的每一台机器共享
got was that each machine share of the
路由交换机或整个网络的
route switch or of the total network
容量为只有每秒50兆比特
capacity was only 50 megabits per second
每秒在其设置50兆位
per second in their setup 50 megabits
每机器，然后威力第二
per second per machine and then might
看起来好像很多50兆天哪
seem like a lot 50 megabits gosh
数以百万计，但它实际上是
millions and millions but it's actually
相比如何快速一盘相当小
quite small compared to how fast a disks
罗恩或CPU上运行，因此这与他们的
Ron or CPUs run and so this with their
网络每秒此50兆比特是
network this 50 megabits per second was
就像一个巨大的限制，所以他们
like a tremendous limit and so they
真正站在自己的头
really stood on their heads in the
在本文设计描述，以避免
design described in the paper to avoid
利用网络和他们打一个
using the network and they played a
一堆花样，以避免发送的东西
bunch of tricks to avoid sending stuff
在网络上时，他们可能
over the network when they possibly
可避免其中之一是他们
could avoid it one of them was they
他们会跑了GFS服务器和
would they ran the gfs servers and the
在同一组的MapReduce的工作人员
MapReduce workers on the same set of
机，因此他们有一千个
machines so they have a thousand
机器他们会运行GFS他们实施
machines they'd run GFS they implement
上千元的GFS服务
their GFS service on that thousand
机运行MapReduce的同一
machines and run MapReduce on the same
1000台机器，然后在
thousand machines and then when the
师傅被分裂了地图和工作
master was splitting up the map work and
排序的养殖出来不同
sort of farming it out to different
工人将巧妙地当它是
workers it would cleverly when it was
即将运行正想地图
about to run the map that was going to
从输入文件中读取一个将图
read from input file one it would figure
从出GFS的服务器实际持有
out from GFS which server actually holds
它的本地磁盘，并将其输入一个文件
input file one on its local disk and it
会送地图为输入文件
would send the map for that input file
在同一个MapReduce的软件
to the MapReduce software on the same
机，以便在默认情况下这个箭头
machine so that by default this arrow
从竟是当地的本地读
was actually local local read from the
本地磁盘并没有涉及
local disk and did not involve the
网络，你知道这取决于
network and you know depending on
故障或负载或什么是
failures or load or whatever that
不能总是这样做，但几乎所有的
couldn't always do that but almost all
地图上会非常相同的运行
the maps would be run on the very same
机和存储从而节约了数据
machine and stored the data thus saving
他们大量的时间，他们将
them vast amount of time that they would
否则必须等待移动输入
otherwise had to wait to move the input
通过网络下招数据
data across the network the next trick
他们打出的是，地图正如我所说
they played is that map as I mentioned
前门店对当地这个输出
before stores this output on the local
本机的磁盘，你跑地图
disk of the machine that you run the map
上，从而再次存储的输出
on so again storing the output of the
地图不需要网络
map does not require network
通信他马上不
communication he's not immediately
因为输出存储在盘
because the output stored in the disk
但是我们确实知道这种或那种方式
however we know for sure that one way or
另一个以组在一起的所有
another in order to group together all
你知道的方式MapReduce的是
of you know by the way the MapReduce is
为了定义为组在一起的所有
defined in order to group together all
与给定的相关联的值的
of the values associated with the given
关键并将它们传递到一个调用
key and pass them to a single invocation
生产一些机器上这是怎么回事
to produce on some machine this is going
要求网络通信我们
to require network communication we're
要你知道，我们要需要获取
gonna you know we want to need to fetch
所有托架，并给他们一个单
all bays and give them a single
机器有跨越移动
machine that have to be moved across the
网络，因此这本洗牌
network and so this shuffle this
键的移动距离是怎么样的
movement of the keys from is kind of
最初由行和在同一存储
originally stored by row and on the same
机器跑，我们需要他们的地图
machine that ran the map we need them
本质上通过柱上被存储在
essentially to be stored on by column on
那将是机器
the machine that's going to be
负责减少这种
responsible for reduce this
行内存储的改造
transformation of row storage
实质上列存储被称为
essentially column storage is called the
文件呼吁洗牌，它确实是
paper calls a shuffle and it really that
移动所需的每一块的数据的
required moving every piece of data
对面的映射网络
across the network from the map that
它产生的减少会
produced it to the reduce that would
需要它，现在它就像昂贵的
need it and now it's like the expensive
MapReduce的一部分呀
part of the MapReduce yeah
你说得对，你能想象一个不同
you're right you can imagine a different
定义中，你有一个更亲切
definition in which you have a more kind
流的减少，我不知道我
of streaming reduce I don't know I
没有经过我认为这不
haven't thought this through I don't
知道为什么这是否是可行的
know why whether that would be feasible
或不肯定，只要程序员
or not certainly as far as programmer
接口一样，如果目标的
interface like if the goal their
头号目标真的能够
number-one goal really was to be able to
人们可以很容易地计划谁
make it easy to program by people who
只是没有在发生了什么事的想法
just had no idea of what was going on in
该系统因此它可能是你知道
the system so it may be that you know
这种斑点，这是真正的方式减少
this speck this is really the way reduce
功能看，你知道在C ++或
functions look and you know in C++ or
类似的流媒体版本
something like a streaming version of
这是现在开始看我不
this is now starting to look I don't
知道它是如何看可能不是这样
know how it look probably not this
符号，但你也许知道这可能是
symbol but you know maybe it could be
这样做的方式，事实上许多现代
done that way and indeed many modern
系统的人得到了很多更
systems people got a lot more
复杂与现代的东西，
sophisticated with modern things that
是接班人的MapReduce和
are the successors the MapReduce and
他们确实涉及处理
they do indeed involve processing
数据流往往不是这样
streams of data often rather than this
很分批进场有一批
very batch approach there is a batch
在这个意义上接近，我们等到
approach in the sense that we wait until
我们得到的所有数据，然后我们处理
we get all the data and then we process
它所以首先你接下来要
it so first of all that you then have to
具有有限的输入权的概念
have a notion of finite inputs right
现代系统经常做你的确
modern systems often do indeed you
流和并能够利用
streams and and are able to take
优势一些效率的做
advantage of some efficiencies do that
MapReduce的好了，所以这是在点
MapReduce okay so this is the point at
此洗牌是所有
which this shuffle is where all the
网络流量会发生这可以
network traffic happens this can
实际上是数据的大量所以如果
actually be a vast amount of data so if
你想想那种如果你选
you think about sort if you're sorting
排序的输出具有相同
the the output of the sort has the same
大小输入到排序，以便
size as the input to the sort so that
这意味着，如果你是，你知道，如果你的
means that if you're you know if your
输入数据的10个TB的你
input is 10 terabytes of data and you're
运行你移动10排序
running a sort you're moving 10
通过网络在万亿字节的数据
terabytes of data across a network at
这点和你的输出也将是
this point and your output will also be
10个TB的，因此这是相当多
10 terabytes and so this is quite a lot
数据，然后它的确是从任何
of data and then indeed it is from any
MapReduce作业虽然不是所有有
MapReduce jobs although not all there's
一些显著减少
some that significantly reduce the
在这些阶段某人的数据量
amount of data at these stages somebody
提到哦，如果你想进什么
mentioned Oh what if you want to feed
减少输出到另一个
the output of reduce into another
MapReduce工作，事实上，这是常
MapReduce job and indeed that was often
什么人想做的事和
what people wanted to do and
在案件的输出减少威力
in case the output of the reduce might
是巨大的像四个排序或网页和
be enormous like four sort or web and
混合输出的上十产生
mixing the output of the produces on ten
输入的兆兆字节的输出
terabytes of input the output of the
再次降低了要去有十数TB等等
reduces again gonna be ten terabytes so
的减小输出也被存储
the output of the reduce is also stored
在GFS和系统，你会知道
on GFS and the system would you know
减少只会产生这些关键
reduce would just produce these key
值对但MapReduce框架
value pairs but the MapReduce framework
将收集起来，并写入到
would gather them up and write them into
在GFS等有巨大的文件
giant files on GFS and so there was
另一轮网络通信的
another round of network communication
让每个输出所需
required to get the output of each
减少对GFS服务器需要
reduce to the GFS server that needed to
存储减少和，因为你可能
store that reduce and because you might
认为他们可以发挥的
think that they could have played the
同一特技与存储的输出
same trick with the output of storing
政府飞行服务队的服务器，从而使输出
the output on the GFS server that
碰巧运行MapReduce的工作人员
happened to run the MapReduce worker
跑的减少，也许他们做
that ran the reduce and maybe they did
这样做，但因为GFS以及
do that but because GFS as well as
性能也分割数据
splitting data for performance also
保持两个或三个副本故障
keeps two or three copies for fault
宽容是手段，不管你是什么
tolerance that means no matter what you
需要写入数据的一个副本
need to write one copy of the data
通过网络到另一台服务器
across a network to a different server
所以有很多网络
so there's a lot of network
这里的沟通和这里还一堆
communication here and a bunch here also
我是这样的网络通信
and I was this network communication
真正限制了吞吐量
that really limited the throughput in
MapReduce的
MapReduce
在2004年到2020年，因为这网络
in 2004 in 2020 because this network
安排是这样一个限制因素
arrangement was such a limiting factor
这么多东西的人想做的事
for so many things people wanted to do
在数据中心的现代数据中心
in datacenters modern data center
网络有很多在根快
networks are a lot faster at the root
莫过于此了，所以你知道一个
than this was and so you know one
典型的数据中心网络你可能
typical data center network you might
今天看到其实有很多根，而不是
see today actually has many root instead
单根的切换一切
of a single root switch that everything
要经过你可能有你
has to go through you might have you
知道许多根交换机和每个机架
know many root switches and each rack
开关具有到每个这些连接
switch has a connection to each of these
排序复制根的开关和
sort of replicated root switches and the
流量是根之间分裂
traffic is split up among the root
切换所以现代数据中心网络
switches so modern data center networks
有吞吐量远远更多的网络和
have far more network throughput and
因为，实际上现代，我认为
because of that actually modern I think
谷歌MapReduce的使用排序的停止
Google sort of stopped using MapReduce a
几年前，但他们停止前
few years ago but before they stopped
使用它的现代MapReduce的实际
using it the modern MapReduce actually
不再试图运行的地图
no longer tried to run the maps on the
同一台计算机上存储的他们的数据
same machine as the data stored on they
很高兴从投票数据
were happy to vote the data from
任何地方，因为他们只是假设
anywhere because they just assumed that
是非常快好我们的出
was extremely fast okay we're out of
时间的MapReduce
time for MapReduce
我们有一个实验室在由于下个月底
we have a lab due at the end of next
周
week
在其中，你会有些写自己
in which you'll write your own somewhat
简化的MapReduce这么有乐趣
simplified MapReduce so have fun with
那
that
看到你在星期四
and see you on Thursday